Guide to the New York State Teachers Association Records 1915-1979
New York State Teachers Association Records
- Series III: Executive Secretary's Files
  - Sub-Series C: Goold Subject Files, 1950-1971, 1950-1971
    - Sub-Series f: General Subject Files, 1950-1970
      - Financing our Schools (From Aug. 1959 Oswego Workshop) (Box 66, Folder 35)
      - Fiscal Independence (Box 66, Folder 36)
      - Review of Fiscal Policy for Public Education in NYS, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 37)
      - Florida Strike (Box 66, Folder 38)
      - Dr. Alice Foley (Box 66, Folder 39)
      - Alice Foley's Address, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 40)
        the quality Elementary school given at council of school. Supt. 9/21/59
      - Requests to Foundations re Financial Support for Studies, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 41)
        1963
      - FTA-future Teachers of America (Box 66, Folder 42)
      - Goold-Conference on Teaching Profession, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 43)
        May 18-19, 1955
      - Mr. G. Howard Goold-Meeting 5/10/68, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 44)
      - Goold Addresses-1950-54, 1950-1954 (Box 66, Folder 45)
      - Goold Addresses-1950-54, 1950-1954 (Box 66, Folder 46)
      - Goold Speeches-Misc. 1951-69, 1951-1969 (Box 66, Folder 47)
      - Goold Speeches and Articles-1955 (Box 66, Folder 48)
      - Mr. Goold's Saturday, March 22, 2 PM Conference Call (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - G. Howard Goold recognition Day, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 2)
        York State Manor, May 2, 1970
      - Goold Speech (Box 67, Folder 3)
        "How can a professional practices Act contribute to the improvement of the quality of teaching service"
      - G.H.G. Speech (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Grievance Procedures for Teachers (Box 67, Folder 5)
        *under 1962 law)
      - Grievance Machinery (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Guidelines-Bylaw 2-1963 (Box 67, Folder 7)
        Membership in Association
      - Guidelines-Bylaw 2- 1963 (Box 67, Folder 8)
        unites of Representation
      - Guidelines 1966 Bylaw 2, Section 3 (Box 67, Folder 9)
        Unites of Representation
      - Guidelines 1966 Bylaw 2, Section 4 (Box 67, Folder 10)
        Chapters
      - Handicapped Children (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Permanent NYSTA Headquarters (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Headquarters Staff-Structure of (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Health Insurance, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 14)
        Possibility re assn. plan for teachers-1959
      - higher Education (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Background Data re Study on Home for Retired Teachers, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 16)
        By Mary Harvey, 1956
      - Home Rule, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Association Studies to be made per 1962 House of Delegates (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Human Relations conference Project (Box 67, Folder 19)
        Buffalo Federation of Teachers
      - Human Relations Conference-Nov. 1-3, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Impasses-Emergency Meetings with Local Representative, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 21)
        Chancellor's hall-June 7, 1969
      - Improving the Quality of Education in New York State (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - Incorporation of Departments (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - In-Service Education (Schuyler County) 1952 (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - In-Service study Programs (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - Integration-1959 (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - Internal Revenue (Box 67, Folder 27)
        Rulings re Expenses for Education
      - IQ Ratings-distribution of 1960 (Box 67, Folder 28)
      - Joint code of Ethics (NYSTA NYSBA) (Box 67, Folder 29)
      - Juvenile Delinquency-1959 (Box 67, Folder 30)
      - Know our Schools Campaign, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 31)
        to improve education and knowledge about it, 1953- 54
      - KUA Program (Box 67, Folder 32)
        Sponsorship of NYS congress of Parents and Teachers and NYSTA
      - Law Regarding Grievance Procedures for Teachers, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 33)
      - Leave of Absence Study (Box 67, Folder 34)
      - Legal Questions-Correspondence, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 35)
      - Legal Rights (Box 67, Folder 36)
      - Legal Service-Policy re (Box 67, Folder 37)
      - Legal Services, Association Assistant in 1963 (Box 67, Folder 38)
      - Legal-Gagnier v. Ockawamick (Columbia County) (Box 67, Folder 39)
      - Legislation-1966 (Box 67, Folder 40)
      - Legislative Bulletins, 1957-1959 (Box 67, Folder 41)
        Other States 1957-59
      - Legislative Bulletins, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 42)
        Other States 1960
      - Legislation-Correspondence to Members, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 43)
      - Legislation-guide for Workers-1956 (Box 67, Folder 44)
        Cumulative
      - Legislation 1967 (Box 67, Folder 45)
        Other Public Employee Relations Bills
      - Call for a Special Session of Legislature, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 46)
        re State Aid, 1969
      - Material for Possible Use re Special Session (Box 67, Folder 47)
        Newspaper clippings, etc. Also see: C-1 proposal
      - Special Session of Legislature, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 48)
        Working Papers, 1969
      - Legislation 1967 (Box 67, Folder 49)
        Implementation of Taylor Law-Materials sent to Supts. And Local Assn. Presidents
      - Legislation 1967 (Box 67, Folder 50)
        Taylor Bill, Implementation of.
      - Legislation 1967-Taylor Bill (Box 67, Folder 51)
        Implementation of-Negotiations Handbook.
      - Legislation (Box 67, Folder 52)
        Correspondence re Taylor Law
      - Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions (Box 67, Folder 53)
      - Joint Legislative Committee on ILR, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 54)
        Public hearings on public employer-employee relations Nov. 28, 1966
      - Legislative Plan, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 55)
        NYSTA-1960
      - Legislative Round-Up, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 56)
        April 26, 1958
      - Lent Amendment re supervisory Dist. Unites of Rep. (Box 67, Folder 57)
      - Lobbying (NEA) (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Public Hearing of NYS Local Assistance Budget (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Local Associations (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Local Associations Presidents, 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Local Associations Presidents, 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Local Law Enforcement and Schools, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 6)
        1954 correspondence re removal of child from schoolroom.
      - Guidelines to Local Leaders (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Local Staff (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Long Island Field Service Office (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Long island Regional Office (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Lottery (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Management Study (Abe Lavine), 1951 (Box 68, Folder 12)
        1951
      - Management Study-Robert Kerker, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 13)
        1969
      - Management Survey-1968 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Management Survey of NYSTA-1969 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Management Study, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 16)
        NYSTA Headquarters, 1968
      - Management Survey, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 17)
        NYSTA-Staff Analysis, 1969
      - Membership-Community Colleges (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Membership Data/Delegates (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Membership Payroll Deduction (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Membership Report (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Membership-Special Letters (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Membership Survey (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Memos to Mr. Streiff re GHG Engagements (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Memos, 1961-1964 (Box 68, Folder 25)
        Re distribution of mail addressed to Mr. Goold, assigned otherwise, 1961- 64
      - Merit Data (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - Merit Rating, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - Moral and Spiritual Training in the Schools, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 28)
        Regents Statement-Nov. 1951
      - Mary Muldoon fund-Misc., 1952-1963 (Box 68, Folder 29)
        Case reports and correspondence and minutes, 1952-63. See Also: Teacher Welfare fund
      - Mary Muldoon Fund, 1960-1965 (Box 68, Folder 30)
        annual reports and financial report, 1960-65
      - NYSTA Membership Mail Survey, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 31)
      - Narcotics-1966 (Box 68, Folder 32)
      - National Assessment of Education (Box 68, Folder 33)
      - National Defense Education Act of 1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 68, Folder 34)
      - Negotiation, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 35)
      - New York City-1953-56, 1953-1956 (Box 68, Folder 36)
      - New York City-1953-56, 1953-1956 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - New York City Bundy Report on Decentralization, 1967-1969 (Box 69, Folder 2)
        1967-69
      - New York City Bundy Report on Decentralization, 1967-1969 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - New York City Decentralization, 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - New York City Decentralization, 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - New York City Schools, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 6)
        Teacher shortage, 1947.
      - New York State Education (Box 69, Folder 7)
        Letters and articles.
      - New York State Legislative Committee, 1954 (Box 69, Folder 8)
        Comics, 1954
      - NYSTA Higher Education Conference, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 9)
        Nov. 3-5, 1966
      - NYSTA Message (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - NYSTA News Trends-General (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - NYSTA-Organizational Study-1968 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - NYSTA-Organizational Study-1968 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - NYSTA-Press Release-9/69, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - NYSTA-Statements of Position (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - NYSTA-Structure (Box 69, Folder 16)
        See Also: Committee to Study NYSTA Structure
      - NYSTA, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 17)
        Trends, 1968-69
      - New York State Teachers Retirement Systems, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 18)
        Minutes-1968
      - Norwalk Impasse (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Oath for Teachers (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - Officer's Meetings- 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 21)
      - Officer's Meetings- 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Officer's Meetings, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 23)
        August 16 with NYS School Board Association-1963
      - Officer's Meeting-June5-6, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - Officer's Meeting-Feb. 9, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Officer's Meeting-March 12, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Officer's Meeting-April 23-24, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 27)
      - Officer's Meeting-Dec. 11, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 28)
      - Oswego Workshop-Aug. 24-27, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 29)
      - Oswego Workshop-1966 (Box 69, Folder 30)
      - Blowing in the Wind, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 31)
        Alice Foley keynote address Oswego Workshop 1966
      - Oswego Wrokship-1967 (Box 69, Folder 32)
        GHG Papers and Notes
      - Oswego Workshop-1967 (Box 69, Folder 33)
      - Past Presidents-Association (Box 69, Folder 34)
      - Patters for Progress by Claude Kulpe (Box 69, Folder 35)
      - Payroll Deductions (Box 69, Folder 36)
        of Association Membership
      - Per Act-1967-69, 1967-1969 (Box 69, Folder 37)
        Correspondence and materials requested
      - Performance Contracting, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 38)
        Letter to Nyquist-1970
      - Place Service (Box 69, Folder 39)
      - Policy Statements, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 40)
      - Political Action II-1967-70, 1967-1970 (Box 69, Folder 41)
      - Political Campaign, 1942, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1942-1950 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Political Party Platforms, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 2)
        Dem and Rep. 1958-Letters to candidates, etc.
      - Political Parties, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 3)
        Platforms, letters to candidates-Cumulative 1954
      - Political Platforms-1932, 1934 (Box 70, Folder 4)
        Education Plank-1934
      - Political Platform, 1944 (Box 70, Folder 5)
        Planks 1948 1952. National Campaign- 1944
      - Political Party 1946 (Box 70, Folder 6)
        Planks re Education-Letters to Candidates-State Campaign
      - Post War Problems of Public Schools (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - President (NYSTA), 1964 (Box 70, Folder 8)
        correspondence with, etc. 1964
      - Press Release (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Private Schools (Box 70, Folder 10)
        Parochial etc. Partnership.Public Schools (Dr. William G. Carr)
      - Print Communications, Report of (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Problem Districts (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Problems of Teacher/ School Board Relations (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Professional Assn.'s with the Board of Regents, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 14)
        Registration of, 1961
      - Professional Autonomy Task Force (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Pro9fessional Growth-Resolution 26 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Professional Negotiation-1963 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Professional Practices Act (Box 70, Folder 18)
        See Professional Education Committee
      - Professional Practices Act, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 19)
        report and reaction, 1956
      - Professional Practice Act, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Professional Practices, Responsibilities and Rights, 1962-1966 (Box 70, Folder 21)
        Commission on 1962-66
      - Professional Responsibility (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Professional Rights and Responsibilities, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 23)
        Third National Workshop-June 24-26, 1964. Seattle, Washington
      - PPR R (Joint) and TEPS Project (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - Professional Sanctions, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 25)
        Progress Report on Study of (1963)
      - Professional Services-Local Leaders Letters (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Professional Services Staff Meeting (Box 70, Folder 27)
      - Professional Standards Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 28)
        annual Reports-1970-71
      - Professors of Educational Administration, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 29)
        National Conference of-1967
      - Public Employment Relations (Box 70, Folder 30)
        (NYSTA Statement)
      - Public Interest in Collective Negotiations in Education (Box 70, Folder 31)
        A paper by George Taylor
      - Pupils Records-1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Public Relations Council, 1960-1970 (Box 70, Folder 33)
        General material 1960-70
      - Pupil Relations Department, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 34)
        Press Release-1966 1967
      - Public Relations Department, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 35)
      - Publications (Box 70, Folder 36)
      - Regents Convocation-Sept. 21, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 37)
      - Regents Proposals, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 38)
        Pursuit of Educational Excellence-1959
      - Regents ProposalsScience and Math 1957-58, 1957-1958 (Box 70, Folder 39)
      - Regents Statement on our Educational Crisis, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 40)
        2/28/58
      - Regional Field Office (Box 70, Folder 41)
      - Regional Offices Network, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - NYSTA (Box 71, Folder 2)
        Network of eight regional offices.
      - Regional Office on Long Island-1964-66, 1964-1966 (Box 71, Folder 3)
        SEE ALSO: Long Island Regional Office
      - Relief Board, 1955-57, 1955-1957 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Relief Board, 1955-57, 1955-1957 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Relief Board, 1955-57, 1955-1957 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Relief Board, 1963-65, 1963-1965 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Reports of Committees, 1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Reports of Committees, 1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Reports of Committees, 1962-65, 1962-1965 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Representation Elections (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Representative Negotiations (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Requests for Assistance-1960 (Box 71, Folder 13)
        Foreign states, etc.
      - Research Department (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Research Questionnaire on Early Secondary Education (Summary) (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Guidelines for Resolving Impasses (1970) (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Retirement, 1944, 1947, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Retirement, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Retirement correspondence, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Association Retirement Program, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Retirement re 1/120th Law, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 21)
        (Chap. 730, Laws of 1956 1957-58 Increased Pension)
      - Retirement re 1/120 Law-1958, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 22)
        Brind letter to C.B. Murray re above Nov. 21, 1957
      - Retirement-Prior Service Credit (Op), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 23)
        Cumulative 1956-57 Brind Opinion, Levitt-Murray-flick-bills, Memos, etc.
      - Retirement-1951-52 (Box 71, Folder 24)
        Work papers re final average salary, prior service credit, supplemental pension
      - Retirement Problems (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - Retirement Systems-Comparison of (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Retiring President (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson (Box 71, Folder 28)
        speeches re education/ budget
      - Rural School Improvement Society (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Salaries-SUNY Colleges 1957-59, 1957-1959 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Memorandum on Need for a Higher Mandated Salary Schedule in NYS (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Memorandum on Need for A Higher Mandated Salary Schedule in NYS (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Saratoga Springs Survey, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 33)
        RE: Superintendents firing possible violation of code of ethics 1960
      - Saratoga Springs Survey, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 34)
        re: Superintendents firing possible violation of code of ethics 1960
      - Save the Children Federation, 1951-53, 1951-1953 (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Scholarships and Loan Funds (Box 71, Folder 36)
        Local Associations
      - School Administration (Box 71, Folder 37)
      - Schools and American Culture (Box 71, Folder 38)
      - School Boards (Box 71, Folder 39)
      - School Bond Authority, 1957-1959 (Box 71, Folder 40)
        Cumulative-1957-59
      - School Buildings (Box 71, Folder 41)
      - School Campus (Box 71, Folder 42)
      - School and Community (Box 71, Folder 43)
      - School Day, Length of (Box 71, Folder 44)
      - School of Education-Council-Cornell, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 1)
        Mr. Goold-Personal 1962
      - Shapiro, George M. (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Sheldon, Dr., Tues., April 13, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Sick Leave (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Sick Leave for Teachers (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Alfred E. Smith Award (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Social Security, 1954-56, 1954-1956 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Social Security, 1955-57, 1955-1957 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Social Security, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Social Secuirty-1957 Referendum (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Social Secuirty-1957 to Present (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Social Secuirty-1960-68, 1960-1968 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Social Secuirty-1965 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Staff-Annual Reports-1962 (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Staff, NYSTA (Box 72, Folder 15)
        Negotiation services staff assignments.
      - Staff Cabinet Meeting, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 16)
        Nov. 30, 1965
      - Staff Conference, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 17)
        Miss Weeks, Sept.. 7, 1960
      - Staff Handbook and Second Draft (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Staff Handbook and Second Draft (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - Staff Meeting, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Staff Meeting, Professional (Box 72, Folder 21)
        Oct. 16, 1993
      - Staff Meeting, Professional, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 22)
        Nov. 9, 1964
      - Staff Meeting, Professional, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 23)
        Jan. 11, 1965
      - Staff Memorandums, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - Staff Memorandums (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Staff Memorandums 1960 (Box 72, Folder 26)
      - Staff Memorandums 1960 (Box 72, Folder 27)
      - Staff Memorandums 1961 (Box 72, Folder 28)
      - Staff Memorandums 1961 (Box 72, Folder 29)
      - Staff Memorandums 1962 (Box 72, Folder 30)
      - Staff Memorandums 1962 (Box 72, Folder 31)
      - Staff Memorandums 1963 (Box 72, Folder 32)
      - Staff Memorandums 1963 (Box 72, Folder 33)
      - Staff Memorandums, Jan-July 1964 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Staff Memorandums, Jan-July 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Staff Memorandums, 1964-66, 1964-1966 (Box 73, Folder 3)
        Dr. Burke Mr. Streiff
      - Staff Memorandums, 1964-66, 1964-1966 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Staff Memos, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 5)
        General-1966
      - Staff Memos, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 6)
        Dr. Kullman-1966
      - Staff Memos (Box 73, Folder 7)
        Alan Lewis
      - Staff Memos (Box 73, Folder 8)
        Curtiss B. Matterson
      - Staff Memos (Box 73, Folder 9)
        Lois Wilson
      - Staff Salaries, 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 10)
        1968-69
      - State Affiliates-1962 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - State Aid Equalization Principle, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 12)
        Statements re by Harrison, Ives, etc. 1954
      - State Aid-1954-55 (Box 73, Folder 13)
        New York City Position
      - State Aid (Box 73, Folder 14)
        Equity in Distribution Effects of Equalization. Rates. MeasurementLocalAbility
      - State Aid-"Basic Aid", 1956 (Box 73, Folder 15)
        Collection of bills (1956) re building aid, non-residents, etc.
      - State Aid, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 16)
        State Aid SEE ALSO-C1 Proposal
      - State Education Associations, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 17)
        Dying or Not by Arvid Burke, 1966
      - State Education Department (Box 73, Folder 18)
        State Education Dept. See Also: NYSTA Resolutions
      - State Education Department-1959 (Box 73, Folder 19)
        Commissioner
      - State Education Department-1960 (Box 73, Folder 20)
        RegentsQuality Education
      - State Education Problems and (Box 73, Folder 21)
        the Responsibility of the Profession by James Allen
      - State Leaders Workshop Day, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 22)
        Oct. 31, 1964
      - State Leaders Workshop, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - State Local Relationships-1963-65, 1963-1965 (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - State Local Relationships-1963-65, 1963-1965 (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - State Salary Law (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - Streiff-Speeches (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - Student Division-May 1961 (Box 73, Folder 28)
      - Student Division-May 1961 (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - Student Education Assn. Handbook, 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - Subversives-State Education Dept., 1953 (Box 73, Folder 31)
        1949 1953
      - Syracuse Study council (Box 73, Folder 32)
        Professional Negotiations
      - Syracuse University American Assembly (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - Tax Annuity Plan, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 34)
      - Tax Sheltered Annuities (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - Tax Sheltered Annuities (Box 73, Folder 36)
      - Taylor Law (Box 74, Folder 1)
        File memos re local representation elections
      - Teacher Aides, 1956-64, 1956-1964 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Teacher Associations (NYS) (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Teacher Certification Requirements (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Teacher's Home (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Teachers, Home for Retired, 1954-1955 (Box 74, Folder 6)
        1954-55
      - Teachers Home, 1959-1967 (Box 74, Folder 7)
        Board of Trustees, 1959-60, 1961, 1964, 1967
      - Teachers Home, 1959-1967 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Teachers Home, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 9)
        New York State Manor-=Financial Statements, 1964
      - Teachers Home Campaign Fund (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Teacher Oath (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Teacher Recognition, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Teacher's Retirement System (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Teacher School-Board Relationships (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Teacher School-Board Relationships, 1961-1965 (Box 74, Folder 15)
        1961-65
      - Teacher School-Board Relationships, 1961-1965 (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - Teacher School-Board Relationships, 1961-1965 (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Teacher School-Board Relationships, 1961-1965 (Box 74, Folder 18)
      - Teacher School-Board Relationships, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 19)
        1967